https://mhcm.org/support/giving/donor-and-member-privacy-policy/

Birthday Parties
Baby’s First Birthday!
Donor and Member Privacy Policy
The Mid-Hudson Children’s Museum subscribes to the following Donor and Member Privacy Policy as it relates to the protection of our donors’ and members’ personal information:
Any information supplied by, or collected from Mid-Hudson Children’s Museum donors and members is confidential. Donor and member information will not be shared outside the Mid-Hudson Children’s Museum for any reason unless permission is granted in writing by the donor/member to share such information.
All requests to remain anonymous will be honored.
The Mid-Hudson Children’s Museum does not share, trade or sell donors’ or members’ personal or contact information with anyone else, nor will the Mid-Hudson Children’s Museum send mailings to donors/members on behalf of other organizations.
Donors and members will be contacted periodically by postal mail, telephone or email for purposes of solicitation, membership renewal, gift acknowledgement and/or to share event information. Donors/members may request in writing to be permanently removed from the Mid-Hudson Children’s Museum mailing list. All requests to be removed from mailing lists shall be honored.
The Mid-Hudson Children’s Museum’s Donor and Member Privacy Policy is posted on the Mid-Hudson Children’s Museum website and is to be listed in all annual reports.
Giving
Ways to Give
Planned Giving
Donor and Member Privacy Policy
Sponsorship
Sponsor Benefits
Current Sponsorship Opportunities
Corporate Membership
